<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<teachers>
    <teacher>
        <name>Mrs. Jianhua Shen</name>
        <title>Instructor of Grade 4 Heritage Chinese Class</title>
        <bioEN>Mrs. Shen is a faculty member at the Department of East Asian Languages and Literatures at Yale University, where she has taught Chinese since 2003. Previously, she also taught Chinese at Harvard University. Mrs. Shen holds a B.A. and a M.A. in Chinese Literatures. Mrs. Shen brings to our school her love of children, passion for teaching and rich experiences. 
        </bioEN>
        <bioCH>沈建华老师是耶鲁大学东亚系资深中文教师。她自2003年到现在在耶鲁大学中文部教授中文。之前，沈老师也曾在哈佛大学和北京语言大学教授中文。沈老师本科和研究生均毕业于首都师范大学中文系。沈老师热爱教育，有爱心，经验丰富, 她在我校教授4年级华裔班中文。
        </bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name>Mrs. Marilyn Guerrera</name>
        <title>Instructor of AP Chinese, Adults Chinese, and Grade 6 Non-heritage Chinese Classes</title>
        <bioEN>Mrs. Guerrera is currently a doctoral candidate in Teaching Chinese as a Second/Foreign Language at Xiamen University. Prior to her doctoral studies, Mrs. Guerrera had been a Chinese teacher at high schools and community college in Connecticut for over five years. She is also a College Board/ETS AP reader. Mrs. Guerrera has extensive experiences in teaching both heritage and non-heritage students. 
        </bioEN>    
        <bioCH>林怡玲老师目前在厦门大学的对外汉语教学专业攻读博士学位。她此前在康州的中学和社区大学从事超过五年的中文教学工作。林老师还是美国大学理事会AP 中文考试的阅卷人。林老师有丰富的教学经验，她的学生既包括华裔也包括非华裔的学生。
        </bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name>Mr. Michael Patrick</name>
        <title>Instructor of SSAT, Creative Writing Classes</title>
        <bioEN>Mr. Patrick is certified in high school English. He has many years of teaching experience at both high school and college levels. Mr. Patrick is a recipient of numerous awards in writing and journalism. He is also a frequent contributor to a number of national and local media outlets, including New York Times. Mr. Patrick holds a B.S. in Media Studies and a M.S. in Journalism.
        </bioEN>         
        <bioCH>Patrick老师持有康州高中英文教师资格证，他还在高中和大学里任教多年。Patrick老师还经常给全国性和地方的媒体撰稿，他的文章曾发表在纽约时报等有影响力的媒体上。他还获得过许多新闻界的奖项。Patrick老师拥有新闻传媒专业学士和硕士学位。
        </bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name>Grandmaster Aiping Cheng</name>
        <title>Instructor of Tai Chi Class</title>
        <bioEN>Grandmaster Cheng is a world renowned Tai Chi and Kung Fu master. Throughout her long and prominent career, she has earned numerous awards including national championships in Tai Chi and Wu Shu. As a member of Chinese National Martial Arts Delegation, she was awarded the Presidential Gold Medal by President Richard Nixon at the White House in 1974. Since she came to the United States in 1997, Grandmaster Cheng has devoted to teaching martial arts among youth and adults, her martial arts school has trained over one thousand students during the past ten years. She was listed in “World Top 100 Martial Arts Masters” in 2008. More details on her background and accomplishments can be found on her website: www.aiping-taichi.com
        </bioEN>         
        <bioCH>程爱萍大师一九七一年初选入浙江省武术队。是全国少数在武术，太极拳两方面都获的成功的武术界名人。在美国担任国际武术散手道联盟荣誉顾问，美国传统武术联合会、康州省主席，美国武当太极馆馆长。程大师1981-1984年就读于上海体育学院武术系。曾三次获得全国武术、太极拳锦标赛冠军，三次亚军。一九八六年应中国武术研究院的邀请，参加了首次全国太极拳竞赛规则的编写工作。并参加太极拳竞赛套路教学片的拍摄，为孙式太极拳竞赛套路教学片做示范动作。一九七四年，应尼克松总统的邀请，随中国武术队访问美国，并在白宫接受总统接见和总统金奖。以后共六次被选入中国武术队走遍五大洲十六个国家。为伊丽莎白女王、西哈努克亲王等各国领袖和人民表演中国传统武术。一九九九年四月在美国建立美国武当武术馆。十年来，有上千人接受训练，连续五年成功举办 “中国春节晚会”。二零零六年，还荣幸的被选入世界联合国 “中国春节晚会”的表演。二零零八年被评为“世界武林百杰”。
        </bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name>Dr. Heather Wainwright</name>
        <title>Instructor of Youth Public Speaking Class </title>
        <bioEN>Dr. Wainwright is a new member of the SCCS community. She has many years of experiences teaching subjects on philosophy, critical thinking, research and expository writing at both college and k-12 level. She holds a B.A. in English and Philosophy from Boston College, and a Ph.D. in philosophy from University of Minnesota. 
        </bioEN>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name>Dr. Bernd Kaiser</name>
        <title>Instructor of Chess I Class</title>
        <bioEN>Dr. Kaiser currently works at a biotechnology company in Connecticut. He obtained his Ph.D. at the Westfaelische Wilhelms Universitaet in Muenster, Germany. After coming to the U.S. for a post-doctoral appointment at MIT, he has been working in the pharmaceutical industry field since. Dr. Kaiser was a chess teacher at CCSU Chinese School in West Hartford for 2 years before joining here at SCCS. 
        </bioEN>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
        <name> Ms. Anna Bu Lei Tu</name>
        <title> Instructor of Advanced Drawing, Art I Classes</title>
        <bioEN>Ms. Tu is a local artist, teacher, and designer. She attended University of the Arts London, School of the Art Institute of Chicago, and Educational Center for the Arts in New Haven Connecticut. Her areas of focus include drawing, design, photography, painting, and Art History. Her work can be viewed at: http://buleitu.tumblr.com/ 
        </bioEN>          
        <bioCH>涂步雷老师是一位艺术家，教师，和设计师。她毕业于伦敦艺术大学，芝加哥艺术学院。 她还在纽黑文的艺术教育中心接受过培训。她的专长包括绘画，设计，摄影，和艺术史。
        </bioCH>
    </teacher>
   <teacher>
        <name>Jim Huang</name>
        <title>Instructor of Debate Class</title>
       <bioEN>Jim Huang, an Ethics, Politics, and Economics major at Yale, was one of the top high-school debaters in the country. He has taught and trained students at some of the nation's best debate camps. He also achieved perfect scores on his ACT, SAT Writing and Reading, and all of his AP courses. In his spare time, Jim does advocacy work and research on a number of underprivileged New Haven communities. He is also a charismatic, poised, and thoughtful person who would be a great role model for any teen. (Jim will also be teaching Creative Writing Class 2 this semester.)
         </bioEN>
       <bioCH></bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
          <name>Karen Young</name>
          <title>Instructor of SSAT Preparation</title>
          <bioEN>Karen Young is a sophomore at Yale University and planning to major in Economics and possibly Political Science. Hailing from Houston, TX, Karen competed in multiple state and national mathematics competitions in high school including TMSCA and AIME, and scored perfectly on her SAT Writing and Reading, Math and Physics SAT II, and multiple AP exams. 
          </bioEN>
         <bioCH></bioCH>
    </teacher>
    <teacher>
    <name>Armando Ghinaglia</name>
    <title>Instructor of SAT Preparation</title>
      <bioEN>Armando Ghinaglia is a graduate of Yale with a degree in Political Science (with distinction in the major). Armando received a cumulative score of 2390 on his SATs (800 Math, 800 Writing, 790 Reading). Over the past year, he worked for Yale as a Woodbridge Fellow in the Office of the Secretary and Vice President for Student Life. This year, he will be attending the Yale Divinity School. Armando has a great amount of experience tutoring for standardized tests and school subjects.
     </bioEN>
     <bioCH></bioCH>
</teacher>
</teachers>